Hello?
Can you hear me?
We hear you loud and clear, Commander.
Go ahead.
Perfect.
Can you see me okay?
We've got you crystal clear.
We're all watching, Ha.
Go on.
This is Sol 142 of the Eris Expedition.
And today, today the human race chide.
We came here looking for water.
For minerals.
We found something so much bigger.
Bigger than minerals?
Commander, what did you find?
Life.
We found life.
Living organisms paying.
Right here.
On Mars.
Say that again?
That's, that's historic.
The discovery of the century.
The millennium.
Books.
Movies.
I'm thinking a documentary.
Narrated by me, obviously.
Incredible, Commander.
Truly.
We'll need a name for the species, of
course.
Wait.
Is something moving behind you?
If you're wondering who stands behind me on
this project...
No, Commander Sessing.
Behind you.
Oh, the whole ready drafted my Nobel speech.
Want to hear the opening?
We are talking six or seven figures here.
Easy.
Not money.
A creature.
There's a creature right behind your crewmate.
A feature.
Yes, the key feature of the whole expedition.
Commander, listen to me.
It's, oh God, it's got a rope.
Hope?
There's nothing but hope now, my friend.
No, it's grabbing him.
It's got Dave.
Grabbing the moment.
Yes, my.
Seize it.
That's the spirit, Houston.
He's tied up.
It's tying him up.
Do something.
Tongue tied, I know, Gray.
It's an emotional day for us.
As you can see, the situation here is
completely under control.
Anyway, that's the discovery.
Questions, Houston?
Commander, there...
You're being awfully quiet.
Stunned into silence, I imagine.
Hello?
Why is everyone so quiet?